more details about the associate. Previously,
I have shared you the video, which shows
the difference between associate and the operator role.
Associate role is built for
the people and the company who are in the ecosystem, such
as traders, importers, exporters,
warehouse owners, inland transportation,
freight forwarders , logistics  providers, suppliers,
packaging companies, quality testing labs,
and agri tech companies. custom clearance agencies, finance
and insurance partners, and procurement partners. Through
obaol, we are creating a one-stop solution. And
Through a beer, we are creating a one, so, through
a beer, we are creating a one-stop solution. And
bringing up all the and bringing up all
the sectors into a one platform. We
are having dedicated features for, We
are having dedicated features for each of the room.
I'll be sharing features We
are having dedicated features for each of
the road. And we are. And
also, Also,
we are adding up more features day by day. I'll
be sharing you another dedicated. I'll be sharing another
videos. We'll be sharing. We'll
be sharing another videos. We'll be sharing another
videos. We'll
be sharing another, we'll be sharing other videos which
showcases the features. Which
showcases, which showcases us the We'll
be sharing other videos which showcase the features and
which our role can be get benefited with that. How
you can be a how you can be an associate. Onboarding
to the platform, active your service, execute with
other roles. Execute
with the other roles. Execute
with other roles and the facilities of the platform. As
be an, as be an associate. SBN
associate, you are bringing up your services and products
into one stop, you are bringing
up your services and product into a one stop
solution execution plan. You
are bringing up your services. As
an associate, you are bringing up your services and
products into a
one stop trade execution platform. Join
as a hope. Join as an associate
now. I'll be. Join
as an officer. Join
as an associate now. Thank you for watching.